# Vinny Vu

Email: vinny.vu.97@gmail.com Mobile: 0420 886 457

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vinny-vu-809bb1139/

# Objective

Vinny is currently completing a Master's in Business Analytics at Monash Business School. He has 1 year of professional services experience in business advisory and assurance.

As a master's student, Vinny has had exposure to data analysis, collaborative practices, and coding in R. Through his experience as an analyst, Vinny was able to gain strong analytical skills through various business engagements, spanning from financial reporting, business assurance, and bringing clarity to day-to-day operations.

# Education

# MASTER OF BUSINESS ANALYTICS | 2020-PRESENT | MONASH BUSINESS SCHOOL

HD average, 82 WAM

# VCE YEAR 12 | 2010-2015 | GLEN WAVERLEY SECONDARY COLLEGE

- Excellence Sports Award 2012, 2014, 2015
- Scholars Award 2015
- Swimming Age Group Captain 2011-2015
- 97.25 ATAR

# BACHELOR COMMERCE (FINANCE AND ACCOUNTING) | 2016-2018 | THE UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE

- 75 WAM
- Professional societies: ASS, FMAA, ASA
- Melbourne University Incline Skating Club

## CTA 1 |2019 | THE TAX INTITUTE

HD

# Skills

- Coding: R, SQL, Python
- Power BI
- Microsoft Excel

 Microsoft office, Xero, MYOB, and QuickBooks

# **Voluntary Work**

## UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE STUDENT UNION | STUDENT MENTOR | 2018

In this role I worked closely with new students offering support through their transition into University and advice on career opportunities/university subjects and majors.

## Responsibilities:

- Events management: working with other mentors in preparing and running of events
- Mentoring: giving advice and direction to new students in regards handling university demands, preparing for their career and other matters
- Long term planning: assist with event planning

#### MS MEGA SWIM | 2018

Participant in the 24hr mega swim to raise money and awareness for multiple sclerosis

FARESHARE | KITCHEN HAND | 2019

#### ANALYST - BUSINESS ADVISORY AND ASSURANCE | PITCHER PARTNERS | 2019

#### VACATIONER | DECEMBER 2017- FEBUARY 2018

- Management Accounting: Monthly management accounts, year-end reporting, income tax returns, activity statements and general business advice to enable clients to make informed business decisions and bring clarity to day-to-day operations
- **Assurance:** Applying risk-based audit and review methodology, pinpointing areas where expert support, advice and action is needed through the analysis of challenges facing the business
- Internal Projects: Research, development, and presentation of an internal development scheme on ways to upskill analysts to firm executives and partners
- Data Analytic Training: attended data analytics pilots and upskilling sessions

#### DATA@ANZ PROGRAM | ANZ | JULY 2020

Using synthesised transaction datasets, I used explanatory and predictive analytic tools to gain an insight into customer behaviour and trends.

#### DATA ANALYTICS CONSULTING VIRTUAL INTERNSHIP | KPMG | JULY 2020

Using analytic tools on client data to conduct a data quality assessment, insights, and insights presentation.

#### DATA VIRUTAL INTERN | COMMONWEALTH BANK | JULY 2020

Generating meaningful information from data to make informed decisions, identify problems and solutions. Using data to build a successful busines and ethics in data analytics.

# Other Experience

# RECREATION LEADER | CITY OF MONASH | 2018

Leading a safe and engaging aquatic leisure program through facilitation of various weekend/party activities.

# Responsibilities

- Weekend/Holiday Program: With strong supervisory and teamwork skill we run games and events focusing on providing professional aquatic programs in a safe a nurturing environment
- **Birthday Parties:** With strong customer service/organisational skills I coordinate children's birthday parties and liaise with parents to ensure the event is enjoyable and safe.

### CITY OF MONASH | LEARN TO SWIM INSTRUCTOR | 2018

- Swimming Instructor: Teaching children to be safe around water and to improve their ability to swim.
- Developing Lesson Plans

# SWIMMING COACH/ MANAGEMENT | BABIES TO KIDS SWIMMING | 2016 - 2018

- Customer Management: Liaising with parents on payment, lesson schedules or any issues with their child to help make the swim ming pool more open and organized. Marketing and online promoting
- Running of events: Leading the running of events such as the annual diving clinic and swim meet

PRIVATE TUTOR - VCE MATHEMATICS AND PHYSICS | DECEMBER 2015- 2018

# **Professional Referees**

Provided upon request